Soutar, Douglas H. Papers 5914
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Soutar Speeches. (Box 19)
  - Executive Enterprises Arlington, Va Feb. 19-20, 1981 (Folder 4 of 6) (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Executive Enterprises Arlington, Va Feb. 19-20, 1981 (Folder 5 of 6) (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Executive Enterprises Arlington, Va Feb. 19-20, 1981 (Folder 6 of 6) (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - DS Speech- University of Arizona "Prospects for the 1980 Nonferrous Negotiations" 3/12-14/80 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - N.Y.T. 4-27-80 Raskin "The Labor Leader as Company Director", 1980 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Center for Continuing Education Washington, D.C. 11-28-78 Wage- Price Guidelines Panel, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - "The I.L.O." World Trade Institute N.Y.C. 12-11-78, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - DS speech - Chicago- 10/2/78 National Safety Congress -" Role of Management in Mine Safety", 1978 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Research & Trading Corporation, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Vassar College "The American Labor Movement: Leadership in Transition" 4/9/79, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Problems at the Bargaining Table: What's Ahead? Management View- point 5-24-79 AAA, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - DS Speech Automation House-TV Series February 16&17, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Soutar Speeches (re Pope John!). (Box 20)
  - IRRA - Los Angeles 5-12-78 OSHA, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - DS Speech - Union College - "Private Sector Views", 5-14-77, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Union College- The Academic Register, 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - DS Presentation Personnel, Safety & Health Meet. Wiwam May 21, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - U. of PA. (Wharton) "Managerial Control of Regulation in the '80s" June 11, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - University of Pennsylvania The Wharton School Centennial Conference (Folder 1 of 6), 1981 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    "Managerial Control of Regulation in the '80s"
  - University of Pennsylvania The Wharton School Centennial Conference (Folder 2 of 6), 1981 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - University of Pennsylvania The Wharton School Centennial Conference (Folder 3 of 6), 1981 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - University of Pennsylvania The Wharton School Centennial Conference (Folder 4 of 6), 1981 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - University of Pennsylvania The Wharton School Centennial Conference (Folder 5 of 6), 1981 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - University of Pennsylvania The Wharton School Centennial Conference (Folder 6 of 6), 1981 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - DS Speech- (Unable to participate) Manila - ICC Congress November 22-26, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - University of Notre Dame 1981 Union-Management Conference (Folder 1 of 5) (Box 20, Folder 13)
    Trends Foreseen for Collective Bargaining in the '80s
  - University of Notre Dame 1981 Union-Management Conference (Folder 2 of 5) (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - University of Notre Dame 1981 Union-Management Conference (Folder 3 of 5) (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - University of Notre Dame 1981 Union-Management Conference (Folder 4 of 5) (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - University of Notre Dame 1981 Union-Management Conference (Folder 5 of 5) (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous (meetings and lists). (Box 21)
  - Ferment in Collective Bargaining National Climate and Emerging Trends (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Interim Report + Industrial Relations Research Association, 1963-1990 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Reductions in Force and Reorganizations: Lawful Employer Responses in a Recessionary Economy, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Loading the Scales: The Proposal to Overturn the Mackay Doctrine Policy Paper, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - An Overview of Labor Management Relations in 1983 + Employment Studies Institute, 1983-1989 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - DS Speech-Georgia State U 5/5/83 "An Era of Challenge for Sollec Collective Bargaining, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - "Creative Bargaining-Does It Make Sense as a Future Policy" Phoenix. Arizona 2-7-84, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - DS Remarks at Howard Jenkins Luncheon 10-26-83 Wash., D.C., 1983 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - "The Outlook on Industrial Relation. In the 1980s" Union College Feb. 9, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Speeches Misc., 1968-1972 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Carnegie-Mellon Univ 10-28-82 "Institutional Prospects in Collective Bargaining & Problem Sol, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Encyclical on Human Work Pope John Paul II Comments by V. Day 4-20-83, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - DS Speech Carnegie -Mellon 10-28-82, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - DS Article - NY Times Forum 12-3-82 & Response, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - "An Evaluation of the Institute of Collective Bargaining in Today's Economy" 1/20/83 NLRB Phoenix, Arizona, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - AMM Interview with DS February 10, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - DS Speech - Pace University Discussion of Intl. Bus. Scene Feb. 14, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - AIME Annual Meeting Feb. 15,1982 "An Overview of Management Development in Mining & Other Industries", 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - DS Speech - May 17, 1982 - LPA Wintergreen, Virginia "Bargaining with the Steelworkers" (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Material (Steelabor + DLR Clips) in 1980 Bargaining - S-C-A- N F, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - 1981 Container Bargaining (Folder 1 of 7) (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - 1980 Aluminum Bargaining (Folder 2 of 7) (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - 1980 Basic Steel Bargaining (Folder 3 of 7) (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - 1980 Cu Bargaining (Folder 4 of 7) (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - USWA - Net Worth (Folder 5 of 7), 1980 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - 1980-1 L/ Z + Brass Bargaining (Folder 6 of 7), 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Draft - Speech Union Power- Steel Pan Alum, + NF (Folder 7 of 7), 1982 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Hofstra University Conf. 6/9/82 "A New National Labor Policy? The Impact of Less Regulation", 1982 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - DS Speech - Cornell Seminar Dec. 9, '81 Ithaca, N.Y., 1981 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - U. of Notre Dame "Trends Foreseen for Collective Bargaining in the '80s" June 12,1981 (Folder 1 of 5) (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - U. of Notre Dame "Trends Foreseen for Collective Bargaining in the '80s" June 12, 1981 (Folder 2 of 5) (Box 21, Folder 31)
    Evaluating Productivity Programs and Job Security
  - U. of Notre Dame "Trends Foreseen for Collective Bargaining in the '80s" June 12, 1981, 1972-1982 (Box 21, Folder 32)
- Miscellaneous (meetings and lists). (Box 22)
  - U. of Notre Dame "Trends Foreseen for Collective Bargaining in the '80s" June 12, 1981 (Folder 4 of 5) (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - U. of Notre Dame "Trends Foreseen for Collective Bargaining in the '80s" June 12, 1981, 1981-1983 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - DS Speech Hofstra U. June 9, 1982 (Folder 1 of 4) (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - DS Speech Hofstra U. June 9, 1982 (Folder 2 of 4) (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - DS Speech Hofstra U. June 9, 1982 (Folder 3 of 4) (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - DS Speech Hofstra U. June 9, 1982 (Folder 4 of 4) (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - BR - Construction Committee Contract Language Task Force, 1973-1978 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - BR - Construction Committee - Task Force on Contractor Association Financing, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - BR Construction Committee Construction Industry Cost Effectiveness Task Force, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - BR - Construction Committee - Hiring Hall Task Force, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - BR Construction Committee Meetings 1975 -1977 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - BR - Construction Committee- Jurisdictional Disputes Task Force (Folder 1 of 2), 1971-1977 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - BR - Construction Committee- Jurisdictional Disputes Task Force (Folder 2 of 2), 1969-1972 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - BR - Construction Committee - Legislative Task Force, 1969-1971 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - BR - Construction Committee Membership Subcommittee, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - BR - Construction Committee - Post- CISC Subcommittee, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - BR- Fortune Article 3/27/78 O'Connell's reply 5/22/78, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - BR- Construction Committee - Task Force on Construction Industry Form, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - BR- Construction Committee Meetings, 1971-1976 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - BR - Construction Users Anti-Inflation Roundtable Coordinating Committee (Folder 1 of 2), 1971 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous (meetings and lists). (Box 23)
  - BR - Construction Users Anti-Inflation Roundtable Coordinating Committee (Folder 1 of 2), 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - BR - Construction Users Anti-Inflation Roundtable Coordinating Committee (Folder 2 of 2), 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - The Business Roundtable Construction Committee+ Chemist Club Group, 1974-1983 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Business Roundtable Employee Relations Committee + Industrial Relations Society, Inc., 1978-1982 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Attendance List: The 1984 Hospital Strike in New York City" Labor Relations Chairman's Advisory Council + Subcommittee on Multinational Labor Relations, 1978- 1985 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Meeting of the ORC Fall Conference Group, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - EEOC, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - OFCC, 1971-1975 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Policy and Supporting Positions, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - International Labor Organization, 1957-1984 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    Parts of documents in other Languages
  - International Labor Organization, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    Map of International Organizations- Geneva- most in Spanish(?)
  - National Academy of Arbitrators, The Copper Club, LPA and ILR Brochure, 1947-1983 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Industrial Relations Research Association, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - The Copper Club, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Attendees + Rooming List- IRCS Key Biscayne Conference, 1965-1967 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Policy and Supporting Positions Committee on Post Office and Civil Service House of Representatives, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Pay Board, 1971-1973 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- NaCor. (Box 24)
  - Policy and Supporting Positions Committee on Post Office and Civil Service House of Representatives, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Attendees + Rooming List-IRCS Key Biscayne Conference, 1960-1967 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - The 1983 Directory National Association of Manufacturers Officers, Directors Committees (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Automation House (Ted Kheel), 1979-1983 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - ASARCO + Institute of Collective Bargaining & Group Relations Inc., 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Membership Directory- New York Chapter, Research Advisory Group Membership Roster, 1978-1982 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - The Wharton School Industrial Research Unit- Research Advisory Group Membership Roster, 1975-1980 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Cornell- ILR Advisory Council, 1977-1983 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - School of Management Working Paper Series- A Proposed Predictive Model of Employee Perceptions of Workplace Discrimination, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Labor Update Volume I + Industrial Relations Research Association, 1977-1989 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Labor Policy Association, 1973-1987 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - D. Soutar BR-ERC, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - ORC - Key Biscayne, 1974-1983 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - The Business Roundtable-Construction Committee Contractors Advisory Committee, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - "The Gargoyle", ILR Associates Briefing, and Determinants of Career Change: A Partial Test of A Model, 1983-1989 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Conference on Wage-Price Guidelines, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Status of Federal Employment Issues, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Federal Employment Legislation Status of Issues, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - NLRB, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Lists (Folder 1 of 3), 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- NaCor. (Box 25)
  - Lists (Folder 2 of 3), 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Lists (Folder 3 of 3), 1980-1984 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Lists #2 (Folder 1 of 3), 1983 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Lists #2 (Folder 2 of 3), 1980-1983 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Industrial Research Unit- Research Advisory Group, Secretary's Conference on Phase II- Industrial Relations, 1970-1973 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - NPF, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - NPF (Folder 1 of 4), 1984 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - NPF New York Metropolitan Area (Areas of New Jersey and Connecticut Included) Screening List (Folder 3 of 40, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - NPF Wis. Bar Association Members Indicating Labor Law Specialization or Interest, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - NPF Wis. Bar Association Members Indicating Labor Law Specialization or Interest, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - NaCOR: Future Activities and Board of Trustees (Folder 1 of 4), 1985-1986 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- NaCOR- Activities and Future Directions+ Current Developments, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- NaCOR Financial Statements, Quarterly Progress Report and Plant Closings, 1983-1986 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Newcomer v. Society N.A., 1975-1983 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- NaCOR- Plant and Business Closings, 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- D. Soutar Developments in Employment Law, Practical Employment Law, + The Economic Club of New York, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- (DLR) Current Developments + National Labor Relations Board, 1984-1989 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- MNC's - ILO - DS Trip 1975 (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 26, Folder 7)
- MNC's - ILO - DS Trip 1975 (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 26, Folder 8)
- NaCOR, ILR Cornell, + Newspaper/ Magazine Articles, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- NaCOR + Letters to D. Soutar- General Dynamic Corporation, Noranda, Newmont Mining Corporation, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- NaCOR, Allied + Letters to D. Soutar, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- NaCOR: Activities and Future Directions and Clearing House- Vol. 1 #1, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- NaCOR Brochures+ NaCOR 1500 CEO's (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Clearinghouse: Legislative Status/Analysis Report + NaCOR Documents: Current Developments, Statement in Hearing, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- National Center on Occupational Readjustment, Inc. Financial Statements, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Plant Closings: A Study of Group Termination Legislation Across Canada, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- NaCOR Documents: Sponsorship List, Research Agenda, Meeting Notes, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Newspaper Clippings, NaCOR: Final Report, Clearinghouse Documents, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- NaCOR Board of Trustees Meeting The Grand Hotel, Washington, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Plant Closings Reference Material, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- NaCOR, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- NaCOR- Managing Plant Closings and Occupational Readjustment: An Employer's Guidebook, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Stauffer Chemical Company- Miscellaneous Replys, NaCOR: Supporters to Date, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- NaCOR Documents: Board of Trustees, State by-State Summary of Proposed Plant Closings Legislation, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- NaCOR Memorandum, Board of Trustees Meeting, Lewis Ferman: Chapter 1, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- D.H. Soutar NaCOR Board of Trustees, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- NaCOR- NYO, 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- National Center on Occupational Readjustment, Inc. Board of Trustees Meeting + Education and Labor Committee Subcommittee on Labor- Management Relations, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- NaCOR '87 Testimony, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- NaCOR- Displaced Workers- Plant Closings and Employee Separations A Guide to the Law, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- NaCOR CEO List, National Center on Occupational Readjustment, Inc. + Newspaper Clippings, 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Subcommittee on Multinational Labor Relations Meeting, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Meeting Package Labor Relations Committee Congress of American Industry, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Mainstream Access Inc., 1985 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- BAC "One Voice" Recorded, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- "One Voice", 1972 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- BR CC- Center for Construction Education Texas A&; M University, 1983-1985 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- D. Soutar Newspaper Clippings, The Business Roundtable, IRRA, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Raskin, Abe, 1975-1981 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- British Employ. Comm, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- The Wall Street Journal, 1976-1983 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Wingspread Conference July 20-21- 1979 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- DS Trip - ILO Tripartite Technical Meeting For Mines Other than Coal Mines Geneva, Switzerland January 11-19, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- DS Letter to Prof. Martin Feldstein w/ related material, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- The New York Times, 1976-1978 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Atlanta, 1982-1983 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- The Daily News, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Ditchley, 1969-1971 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- DS Colleges / Universities Pace Univ. - Edward Corsi Insti., 1977-1985 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Pace Oct. 9 Corsi, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Cornell- DS 3-20-72 Letter RE "Business Action Council", 1992 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Soviet Military Power, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- U.K. Clips, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Mac Gregor, 1982-1983 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- The AFL -CIO Platform Proposals, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Strategy for U.S. Industrial Competitiveness, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Fourth Tripartite Technical Meeting for Mines Other than Coal Mines General Report I-III + The Record of the Association of the Bar, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Fourth Tripartite Technical Meeting for Mines Other than Coal Mines General Report I-III + The Record of the Association of the Bar, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Daily Labor Report, The Wallace Miner, Labor Law Newsletter, 1984-1985 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Industrial Relations Research Association Conference Notes and Papers- D. Soutar, 1970-1984 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- ASARCO, Raskin Papers and Newspaper Clippings, 1959-1983 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Daily Labor Report and The Wallace Miner Sept. 19-1 Nov. 20, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Daily Labor Report, The Wallace Miner and Other Newspaper Articles- Spet.4 '84 to Feb.21 '85, 1984-1985 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- The Wallace Miner and Other Newspaper Articles relating to ASARCO, 1984-1985 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Daily Labor Report, The Wallace Miner and Other Newspaper/ Mag. Articles, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Daily Labor Report+ Articles Relating to ASARCO, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Programs in Personnel and Industrial Relations, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Programs in Personnel and Industrial Relations, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Chronicle, ILR and ASARCO News, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- The Business Roundtable, The Anaconda Company and Letters to D. Soutar- Retirement, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Daily Labor Report, The Arizona Daily Star, Articles about ASARCO, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- D. Soutar- ASARCO Incorporated, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Western Electric Grappling with the Giants- Multinational Corporation and Industrial Democracy, Other Newsletters, 1973-1984 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Daily Labor Report, The Wallace Miner, The Union College Chronicle, 1984-1985 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- ASARCO, Capital Formation, AARP, Senate Journal and American Mining Congress Journal, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- American Mining Congress Journal, Union's Week and Other Newspaper Articles, 1972-1983 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- ASARCO News, The Arizona Daily Star, New York and Los Angeles Labor Conference Program and Washington, D.C. Labor Conference, 1966-1985 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- NaCOR -NPF- Trace 4 F, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- NaCOR -NPF- Trace 4 F, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 6)